Guide to the Yale Law School Fund Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Law School Fund records
1963-2004
RU 980
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(1 box)
The records consist of by-laws and minutes of the board of directors of the YLSF, annual reports, brochures and other printed materials documenting fund raising activities of the Yale Law School during 1963-2004.
Yale Law School
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 26-E, Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale Law School
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Yale Law School Fund, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of by-laws and minutes of the board of directors of the YLSF, annual reports, brochures and other printed materials documenting fund raising activities of the Yale Law School during 1963-2004.
Educational fund raising; Fund raising; Law schools -- Administration; Law schools -- Finance; Yale Law School; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Finance
- Minutes, bylaws, annual reports, and printed materials of the Yale Law School Fund, 1963-2004; Accession 2005-A-126
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039
  - A Partner in Excellence: A History of the Yale Law School Fund, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors
    - Bylaws, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1970-2004 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 5)
    - Annual reports, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Review Committee Report, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Yale Law School brochures, 1963-1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - YLSF fund raising brochures, 1971-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9 - 10)
  - Yale Law Report, Spring 1980, Winter 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)